{
  "1": {
    "1": "A computer programming language",
    "2": "An alien language",
    "3": "Another name for Java",
    "4": "A robot name",
    "question": "What is JavaScript?",
    "answer": "A computer programming language"
  },
  "2": {
    "1": "splice(0,1)",
    "2": "pop()",
    "3": "shift()",
    "4": "push()",
    "question": "What is the built-in array method used to remove an element at index 0",
    "answer": "shift()"
  },
  "3": {
    "1": "[ 'rose', 'lily', 'peony', 'jasmine']",
    "2": "jasmine",
    "3": "3",
    "4": "rose",
    "question": "What is printed in the console after the following code runs? const flowers = [ 'rose', 'lily', 'peony', 'jasmine']; console.log(flowers.pop()); ",
    "answer": "jasmine"
  },
  "4": {
    "1": "false",
    "2": "'false'",
    "3": "1",
    "4": "true",
    "question": "What is printed in the console after the following code runs? console.log(false === 'false')",
    "answer": "false"
  },
  "5": {
    "1": "1",
    "2": "NaN",
    "3": "0",
    "4": "2",
    "question": "What is printed in the console after the following code runs? console.log(true + false / true + true)",
    "answer": "2"
  },
  "6": {
    "1": "document.getElement('div').innerHTML = 'Heyyy, Earth!'",
    "2": "document.getElementById('div').innerHTML = 'Heyyy, Earth!'",
    "3": "#quiz.innerHTML = 'Heyyy, Earth!'",
    "4": "document.getElementById('quiz').innerHTML = 'Heyyy, Earth!'",
    "question": "What is the correct JavaScript syntax to change the content of this HTML tag? <div id='quiz'>Hello, World!</div>",
    "answer": "document.getElementById('quiz').innerHTML = 'Heyyy, Earth!'"
  },
  "7": {
    "1": "{/* this is a JS comment */}",
    "2": "// this is a JS comment",
    "3": "<!-- this is a JS comment -->",
    "4": "/ this is a JS comment */",
    "question": "How do you write a comment in JavaScript?",
    "answer": "// this is a JS comment"
  },
  "8": {
    "1": "math.round(3.50)",
    "2": "Math.round(3.50)",
    "3": "Math.down(3.50)",
    "4": "Math.rnd(3.50)",
    "question": "How do you round the number 3.50 to the nearest integer?",
    "answer": "Math.round(3.50)"
  },
  "9": {
    "1": "string greatestBaseballTeam = 'Anaheim Angels'",
    "2": "var greatestBaseballTeam: 'Anaheim Angels'",
    "3": "const greatestBaseballTeam = 'Anaheim Angels'",
    "4": "greatestBaseballTeam = 'Anaheim Angels'",
    "question": "How do you declare a variable in JavaScipt?",
    "answer": "const greatestBaseballTeam = 'Anaheim Angels'"
  },
  "10": {
    "1": "'object'",
    "2": "08Jec7",
    "3": "[ 5, 6, 7, 8 ]",
    "4": "true",
    "question": "Choose the object.",
    "answer": "[ 5, 6, 7, 8 ]"
  },
  "11": {
    "1": "A pure function",
    "2": "An anonymous function",
    "3": "An arrow function",
    "4": "A Java function",
    "question": "What is this? () => {}",
    "answer": "An arrow function"
  },
  "12": {
    "1": "1992",
    "2": "1993",
    "3": "1994",
    "4": "1995",
    "question": "What year was JavaScript introduced?",
    "answer": "1995"
  },
  "13": {
    "1": "Netscape Navigator",
    "2": "Safari",
    "3": "Internet Explorer",
    "4": "Mosaic",
    "question": "Which browser was JavaScript developed for?",
    "answer": "Netscape Navigator"
  }
}
